Jack Benny papers, 1930-1974
UCLA Library Special Collections
- Radio Scripts.
  - The Jello Program.
    - ., November 10, 1940. (Box 14, Folder 1)
    - ., November 17, 1940. (Box 14, Folder 1)
    - ., November 24, 1940. (Box 14, Folder 1)
    - ., December 1, 1940. (Box 14, Folder 1)
    - ., December 8, 1940. (Box 14, Folder 2)
    - ., December 15, 1940. (Box 14, Folder 2)
    - ., December 22, 1940. (Box 14, Folder 2)
    - ., December 29, 1940. (Box 14, Folder 2)
    - ., January 5, 1941. (Box 14, Folder 2)
    - ., January 12, 1941. (Box 14, Folder 2)
    - ., January 19, 1941. (Box 14, Folder 2)
    - ., January 26, 1941. (Box 14, Folder 2)
    - ., February 2, 1941. (Box 14, Folder 2)
    - ., February 9, 1941. (Box 14, Folder 3)
    - ., February 16, 1941. (Box 14, Folder 3)
    - ., March 16, 1941. (Box 14, Folder 3)
    - ., March 23, 1941. (Box 14, Folder 3)
    - ., March 30, 1941. (Box 14, Folder 3)
    - ., April 6, 1941. (Box 14, Folder 3)
    - ., April 13, 1941. (Box 14, Folder 4)
    - ., April 20, 1941. (Box 14, Folder 4)
    - ., April 27, 1941. (Box 14, Folder 4)
    - ., May 4, 1941. (Box 14, Folder 4)
    - ., May 11, 1941. (Box 14, Folder 4)
    - ., May 18, 1941. (Box 14, Folder 4)
    - ., May 25, 1941. (Box 14, Folder 4)
    - ., June 1, 1941. (Box 14, Folder 4)
    - ., October 5, 1941. (Box 15, Folder 1)
    - ., October 12, 1941. (Box 15, Folder 1)
    - ., October 19, 1941. (Box 15, Folder 1)
    - ., October 26, 1941. (Box 15, Folder 1)
    - ., November 2, 1941. (Box 15, Folder 1)
    - ., November 9, 1941. (Box 15, Folder 1)
    - ., November 16, 1941. (Box 15, Folder 1)
    - ., November 23, 1941. (Box 15, Folder 1)
    - ., November 30, 1941. (Box 15, Folder 1)
    - ., December 7, 1941. (Box 15, Folder 2)
    - ., December 14, 1941. (Box 15, Folder 2)
    - ., December 21, 1941. (Box 15, Folder 2)
    - ., December 28, 1941. (Box 15, Folder 2)
    - ., January 4, 1942. (Box 15, Folder 2)
    - ., January 11, 1942. (Box 15, Folder 2)
    - ., January 25, 1942. (Box 15, Folder 2)
    - ., February 1, 1942. (Box 15, Folder 2)
    - ., February 8, 1942. (Box 15, Folder 3)
    - ., February 15, 1942. (Box 15, Folder 3)
    - ., February 22, 1942. (Box 15, Folder 3)
    - ., March 1, 1942. (Box 15, Folder 3)
    - ., March 8, 1942. (Box 15, Folder 3)
    - ., March 15, 1942. (Box 15, Folder 3)
    - ., March 22, 1942. (Box 15, Folder 3)
    - ., March 29, 1942. (Box 15, Folder 3)
    - ., April 5, 1942. (Box 15, Folder 3)
    - ., April 12, 1942. (Box 15, Folder 3)
    - ., April 19, 1942. (Box 15, Folder 3)
    - ., April 26, 1942. (Box 15, Folder 4)
    - ., May 3, 1942. (Box 15, Folder 4)
    - ., May 10, 1942. (Box 15, Folder 4)
    - ., May 17, 1942. (Box 15, Folder 4)
    - ., May 24, 1942. (Box 15, Folder 4)
    - ., May 31, 1942. (Box 15, Folder 4)
    - --Gulf Screen Theatre Guild, Parent by Proxy.., March 29, 1942. (Box 15, Folder 4)
    - --Command Performance, U.S.A., Program #12.., May 3, 1942. (Box 15, Folder 4)
    - --NBC's 15th Anniversary Program.., November 15, 1942. (Box 15, Folder 4)
    - --Packard Motor Car Co.., September 8, 1936. (Box 16, Folder 1)
    - --NBC's 10th Anniversary.., November 7, 1936. (Box 16, Folder 1)
    - --Paramount Silver Jubilee Broadcast.., January 8, 1937. (Box 16, Folder 1)
    - --British Broadcast., February 8, 1937. (Box 16, Folder 1)
    - --Brewster's Millions.., February 15, 1937. (Box 16, Folder 1)
    - --Ben Bernie Program.., March 2, 1937. (Box 16, Folder 1)
    - --Seven Keys to Baldpate.., September 26, 1938. (Box 16, Folder 2)
    - --Screen Guild Show.., January 8, 1939. (Box 16, Folder 2)
    - --March of Dimes Broadcast.., January 21, 1939. (Box 16, Folder 2)
    - --The Tuesday Night Party.., March 16, 1939. (Box 16, Folder 2)
    - --Gulf Screen Theatre Guild.., October 20, 1940. (Box 16, Folder 3)
    - --Maxwell House Coffee Time.., November 21, 1940. (Box 16, Folder 3)
    - --Bundles for Britain.., January 1, 1941. (Box 16, Folder 3)
    - --Special Program for Radio and Movie Guide.., January 19, 1941. (Box 16, Folder 3)
    - --America Calling.., February 8, 1941. (Box 16, Folder 3)
    - --Behind the Mike, Benny Interview.., May 4, 1941. (Box 16, Folder 3)
    - --Special broadcast from Benny's home, NBC 10th Anniversary Dinner.., May 9, 1941. (Box 16, Folder 3)
    - --Millions for Defense.., July 30, 1941. (Box 16, Folder 3)
    - *., October 14, 1934. (Box 17, Folder 1)
    - *., October 21, 1934. (Box 17, Folder 1)
    - *., October 28, 1934. (Box 17, Folder 1)
    - *., November 4, 1934. (Box 17, Folder 1)
    - *., November 11, 1934. (Box 17, Folder 1)
    - *., November 18, 1934. (Box 17, Folder 1)
    - *., December 2, 1934. (Box 17, Folder 1)
    - *., December 9, 1934. (Box 17, Folder 1)
    - *., December 16, 1934. (Box 17, Folder 1)
    - *., December 23, 1934. (Box 17, Folder 1)
    - *., December 30, 1934. (Box 17, Folder 2)
    - *., January 6, 1935. (Box 17, Folder 2)
    - *., January 13, 1935. (Box 17, Folder 2)
    - *., January 20, 1935. (Box 17, Folder 2)
    - *., January 27, 1935. (Box 17, Folder 2)
    - *., February 10, 1935. (Box 17, Folder 2)
    - *., February 17, 1935. (Box 17, Folder 2)
    - *., February 24, 1935. (Box 17, Folder 2)
    - *., March 3, 1935. (Box 17, Folder 2)
    - *., March 10, 1935. (Box 17, Folder 3)
    - *., March 17, 1935. (Box 17, Folder 3)
    - *., March 24, 1935. (Box 17, Folder 3)
    - *., March 31, 1935. (Box 17, Folder 3)
    - *., April 7, 1935. (Box 17, Folder 3)
    - *., April 14, 1935. (Box 17, Folder 3)
    - *., April 21, 1935. (Box 17, Folder 3)
    - *., April 28, 1935. (Box 17, Folder 3)
    - *., May 5, 1935. (Box 17, Folder 3)
    - *., May 12, 1935. (Box 17, Folder 3)
    - *., May 19, 1935. (Box 18, Folder 1)
    - *., May 26, 1935. (Box 18, Folder 1)
    - *., June 2, 1935. (Box 18, Folder 1)
    - *., June 9, 1935. (Box 18, Folder 1)
    - *., June 16, 1935. (Box 18, Folder 1)
    - *., June 23, 1935. (Box 18, Folder 1)
    - *., June 30, 1935. (Box 18, Folder 1)
    - *., July 7, 1935. (Box 18, Folder 1)
    - *., July 14, 1935. (Box 18, Folder 1)
    - *., October 6, 1935. (Box 18, Folder 2)
    - *., October 13, 1935. (Box 18, Folder 2)
    - *., October 20, 1935. (Box 18, Folder 2)
    - *., October 27, 1935. (Box 18, Folder 2)
    - *., November 3, 1935. (Box 18, Folder 2)
    - *., November 10, 1935. (Box 18, Folder 2)
    - *., November 17, 1935. (Box 18, Folder 2)
    - *., November 24, 1935. (Box 18, Folder 2)
    - *., December 1, 1935. (Box 18, Folder 2)
    - *., December 6, 1935. (Box 18, Folder 3)
    - *., December 15, 1935. (Box 18, Folder 3)
    - *., December 22, 1935. (Box 18, Folder 3)
    - *., December 29, 1935. (Box 18, Folder 3)
    - *., January 12, 1936. (Box 18, Folder 3)
    - *., January 19, 1936. (Box 18, Folder 3)
    - *., January 26, 1936. (Box 18, Folder 3)
    - *., February 2, 1936. (Box 18, Folder 3)
    - *., February 9, 1936. (Box 18, Folder 3)
    - *., February 16, 1396. (Box 18, Folder 4)
    - *., February 23, 1936. (Box 18, Folder 4)
    - *., March 1, 1936. (Box 18, Folder 4)
    - *., March 8, 1936. (Box 18, Folder 4)
    - *., March 15, 1936. (Box 18, Folder 4)
    - *., March 22, 1936. (Box 18, Folder 4)
    - *., March 29, 1936. (Box 18, Folder 4)
    - *., April 19, 1936. (Box 18, Folder 4)
    - *., April 26, 1936. (Box 19, Folder 1)
    - *., May 3, 1936. (Box 19, Folder 1)
    - *., May 10, 1936. (Box 19, Folder 1)
    - *., May 24, 1936. (Box 19, Folder 1)
    - *., May 31, 1936. (Box 19, Folder 1)
    - *., June 7, 1936. (Box 19, Folder 1)
    - *., June 14, 1936. (Box 19, Folder 1)
    - *., June 21, 1936. (Box 19, Folder 1)
    - *., December 13, 1936. (Box 19, Folder 2)
    - *., December 20, 1936. (Box 19, Folder 2)
    - *., December 27, 1936. (Box 19, Folder 2)
    - *., January 3, 1937. (Box 19, Folder 2)
    - *., January 10, 1937. (Box 19, Folder 2)
    - *., January 17, 1937. (Box 19, Folder 2)
    - *., January 24, 1937. (Box 19, Folder 2)
    - *., January 31, 1937. (Box 19, Folder 2)
    - *., February 7, 1937. (Box 19, Folder 3)
    - *., February 14, 1937. (Box 19, Folder 3)
    - *., February 21, 1937. (Box 19, Folder 3)
    - *., February 28, 1937. (Box 19, Folder 3)
    - *., March 7, 1937. (Box 19, Folder 3)
    - *., March 14, 1937. (Box 19, Folder 3)
    - *., March 21, 1937. (Box 19, Folder 3)
    - *., March 28, 1937. (Box 19, Folder 3)
    - *., April 4, 1937. (Box 19, Folder 4)
    - *., April 11, 1937. (Box 19, Folder 4)
    - *., April 18, 1937. (Box 19, Folder 4)
    - *., April 25, 1937. (Box 19, Folder 4)
    - *., May 2, 1937. (Box 19, Folder 4)
    - *., May 9, 1937. (Box 19, Folder 4)
    - *., May 30, 1937. (Box 20, Folder 1)
    - *., June 6, 1937. (Box 20, Folder 1)
    - *., June 13, 1937. (Box 20, Folder 1)
    - *., June 20, 1937. (Box 20, Folder 1)
    - *., June 27, 1937. (Box 20, Folder 1)
    - *--NBC's 10th Anniversary Program.., November 7, 1936. (Box 20, Folder 2)
    - *--Paramount Silver Jubilee.., January 8, 1937. (Box 20, Folder 2)
    - *--British Broadcast.., February 8, 1937. (Box 20, Folder 2)
    - *--Brewster's Millions.., February 15, 1937. (Box 20, Folder 2)
    - *--Ben Bernie Program.., March 2, 1937. (Box 20, Folder 2)
    - *--The Packard Hour.., September 8, 1936. (Box 20, Folder 2)
    - *., October 3, 1937. (Box 20, Folder 3)
    - *., October 10, 1937. (Box 20, Folder 3)
    - *., October 17, 1937. (Box 20, Folder 3)
    - *., October 24, 1937. (Box 20, Folder 3)
    - *., October 31, 1937. (Box 20, Folder 3)
    - *., November 7, 1937. (Box 20, Folder 3)
    - *., November 14, 1937. (Box 20, Folder 3)
    - *., November 21, 1937. (Box 20, Folder 3)
    - *., November 28, 1937. (Box 20, Folder 3)
    - *., December 5, 1937. (Box 20, Folder 3)
    - *., December 12, 1937. (Box 20, Folder 4)
    - *., December 19, 1937. (Box 20, Folder 4)
    - *., December 26, 1937. (Box 20, Folder 4)
    - *., January 2, 1938. (Box 20, Folder 4)
    - *., January 9, 1938. (Box 20, Folder 4)
    - *., January 16, 1938. (Box 20, Folder 4)
    - *., January 23, 1938. (Box 20, Folder 4)
    - *., January 30, 1938. (Box 20, Folder 4)
    - *., February 6, 1938. (Box 20, Folder 4)
    - *., February 20, 1938. (Box 20, Folder 4)
    - *., February 27, 1938. (Box 20, Folder 4)
    - *., March 6, 1938. (Box 21, Folder 1)
    - *., March 13, 1938. (Box 21, Folder 1)
    - *., March 20, 1938. (Box 21, Folder 1)
    - *., March 27, 1938. (Box 21, Folder 1)
    - *., April 3, 1938. (Box 21, Folder 1)
    - *., April 10, 1938. (Box 21, Folder 1)
    - *., April 17, 1938. (Box 21, Folder 1)
    - *., April 24, 1938. (Box 21, Folder 1)
    - *., May 1, 1938. (Box 21, Folder 1)
    - *., May 8, 1938. (Box 21, Folder 1)
    - *., May 15, 1938. (Box 21, Folder 1)
    - *., May 22, 1938. (Box 21, Folder 2)
    - *., May 29, 1938. (Box 21, Folder 2)
    - *., June 5, 1938. (Box 21, Folder 2)
    - *., June 12, 1938. (Box 21, Folder 2)
    - *., June 19, 1938. (Box 21, Folder 2)
    - *., June 26, 1938. (Box 21, Folder 2)
    - *--Town Hall Tonite.., December 22, 1937. (Box 21, Folder 2)
    - *--Dale Armstrong Interview.., January 25, 1938. (Box 21, Folder 2)
    - *--American Legion Anniversary Broadcast.., March 15, 1938. (Box 21, Folder 2)
    - *., October 2, 1938. (Box 21, Folder 3)
    - *., October 16, 1938. (Box 21, Folder 3)
    - *., October 23, 1938. (Box 21, Folder 3)
    - *., October 30, 1938. (Box 21, Folder 3)
    - *., November 6, 1938. (Box 21, Folder 3)
    - *., November 13, 1938. (Box 21, Folder 3)
    - *., November 20, 1938. (Box 21, Folder 3)
    - *., November 27, 1938. (Box 21, Folder 3)
    - *., December 4, 1938. (Box 21, Folder 3)
    - *., December 11, 1938. (Box 22, Folder 1)
    - *., December 18, 1938. (Box 22, Folder 1)
    - *., December 25, 1938. (Box 22, Folder 1)
    - *., January 1, 1939. (Box 22, Folder 1)
    - *., January 8, 1939. (Box 22, Folder 1)
    - *., January 15, 1939. (Box 22, Folder 1)
    - *., January 22, 1939. (Box 22, Folder 1)
    - *., January 29, 1939. (Box 22, Folder 1)
    - *., February 5, 1939. (Box 22, Folder 1)
    - *., February 12, 1939. (Box 22, Folder 1)
    - *., February 19, 1939. (Box 22, Folder 1)
    - *., February 26, 1939. (Box 22, Folder 1)
    - *., March 5, 1939. (Box 22, Folder 2)
    - *., March 12, 1939. (Box 22, Folder 2)
    - *., March 19, 1939. (Box 22, Folder 2)
    - *., March 26, 1939. (Box 22, Folder 2)
    - *., April 2, 1939. (Box 22, Folder 2)
    - *., April 9, 1939. (Box 22, Folder 2)
    - *., April 16, 1939. (Box 22, Folder 2)
    - *., April 23, 1939. (Box 22, Folder 2)
    - *., April 30, 1939. (Box 22, Folder 2)
    - *., May 7, 1939. (Box 22, Folder 2)
    - *., May 14, 1939. (Box 22, Folder 2)
    - *., May 21, 1939. (Box 22, Folder 3)
    - *., May 28, 1939. (Box 22, Folder 3)
    - *., June 4, 1939. (Box 22, Folder 3)
    - *., June 11, 1939. (Box 22, Folder 3)
    - *., June 18, 1939. (Box 22, Folder 3)
    - *., June 25, 1939. (Box 22, Folder 3)
    - *--Seven Keys to Baldpate.., September 26, 1938. (Box 22, Folder 3)
    - *--March of Dimes Program.., January 21, 1939. (Box 22, Folder 3)
    - *., October 8, 1939. (Box 23, Folder 1)
    - *., October 15, 1939. (Box 23, Folder 1)
    - *., October 22, 1939. (Box 23, Folder 1)
    - *., October 29, 1939. (Box 23, Folder 1)
    - *., November 5, 1939. (Box 23, Folder 1)
    - *., November 12, 1939. (Box 23, Folder 1)
    - *., November 26, 1939. (Box 23, Folder 1)
    - *., December 3, 1939. (Box 23, Folder 1)
    - *., December 10, 1939. (Box 23, Folder 1)
    - *., December 17, 1939. (Box 23, Folder 1)
    - *., December 24, 1939. (Box 23, Folder 2)
    - *., December 31, 1939. (Box 23, Folder 2)
    - *., January 7, 1940. (Box 23, Folder 2)
    - *., January 14, 1940. (Box 23, Folder 2)
    - *., January 21, 1940. (Box 23, Folder 2)
    - *., January 28, 1940. (Box 23, Folder 2)
    - *., February 4, 1940. (Box 23, Folder 2)
    - *., February 11, 1940. (Box 23, Folder 2)
    - *., February 18, 1940. (Box 23, Folder 2)
    - *., February 25, 1940. (Box 23, Folder 2)
    - *., March 3, 1940. (Box 23, Folder 3)
    - *., March 10, 1940. (Box 23, Folder 3)
    - *., March 17, 1940. (Box 23, Folder 3)
    - *., March 24, 1940. (Box 23, Folder 3)
    - *., March 31, 1940. (Box 23, Folder 3)
    - *., April 7, 1940. (Box 23, Folder 3)
    - *., April 14, 1940. (Box 23, Folder 3)
    - *., April 21, 1940. (Box 24, Folder 1)
    - *., April 28, 1940. (Box 24, Folder 1)
    - *., May 5, 1940. (Box 24, Folder 1)
    - *., May 12, 1940. (Box 24, Folder 1)
    - *., May 26, 1940. (Box 24, Folder 1)
    - *., June 2, 1940. (Box 24, Folder 1)
    - *., June 9, 1940. (Box 24, Folder 2)
    - *., June 16, 1940. (Box 24, Folder 2)
    - Special programs:.
      - *--Salvation Army Program.., December 16, 1939. (Box 24, Folder 2)
      - *--Radio Guide Sketch.., February 10, 1940. (Box 24, Folder 2)
      - *--Campbell Playhouse, June Moon.., March 24, 1940. (Box 24, Folder 2)
      - *--Kate Smith Hour.., April 26, 1940. (Box 24, Folder 2)
      - *--Fred Allen Show. Incomplete.., June 19, 1940. (Box 24, Folder 2)
    - *., February 9, 1941. (Box 24, Folder 3)
    - *., February 16, 1941. (Box 24, Folder 3)
    - ., February 23, 1941. (Box 24, Folder 3)
    - ., March 2, 1941. (Box 24, Folder 3)
    - ., March 9, 1941. (Box 24, Folder 3)
    - *., March 16, 1941. (Box 24, Folder 3)
    - *., March 23, 1941. (Box 24, Folder 3)
    - *., March 30, 1941. (Box 24, Folder 3)
    - *., April 6, 1941. (Box 24, Folder 3)
    - *., April 13, 1941. (Box 24, Folder 3)
    - *., April 20, 1941. (Box 25, Folder 1)
    - *., April 27, 1941. (Box 25, Folder 1)
    - *., May 4, 1941. (Box 25, Folder 1)
    - *., May 11, 1941. (Box 25, Folder 1)
    - *., May 18, 1941. (Box 25, Folder 1)
    - *., May 25, 1941. (Box 25, Folder 1)
    - *., June 1, 1941. (Box 25, Folder 1)
    - *., October 5, 1941. (Box 25, Folder 2)
    - *., October 12, 1941. (Box 25, Folder 2)
    - *., October 19, 1941. (Box 25, Folder 2)
    - *., October 26, 1941. (Box 25, Folder 2)
    - *., November 9, 1941. (Box 25, Folder 2)
    - *., November 16, 1941. (Box 25, Folder 2)
    - *., November 23, 1941. (Box 25, Folder 2)
    - *., November 30, 1941. (Box 25, Folder 2)
    - *., December 7, 1941. (Box 25, Folder 3)
    - *., December 14, 1941. (Box 25, Folder 3)
    - *., December 21, 1941. (Box 25, Folder 3)
    - *., December 28, 1941. (Box 25, Folder 3)
    - *., January 11, 1942. (Box 25, Folder 3)
    - *., January 25, 1942. (Box 25, Folder 3)
    - *., February 1, 1942. (Box 25, Folder 3)
    - *., February 8, 1942. (Box 25, Folder 4)
    - *., February 15, 1942. (Box 25, Folder 4)
    - *., February 22, 1942. (Box 25, Folder 4)
    - *., March 1, 1942. (Box 25, Folder 4)
    - *., March 8, 1942. (Box 25, Folder 4)
    - *., March 15, 1942. (Box 25, Folder 4)
    - *., March 22, 1942. (Box 25, Folder 4)
    - *., March 29, 1942. (Box 25, Folder 4)
    - *., April 5, 1942. (Box 26, Folder 1)
    - *., April 12, 1942. (Box 26, Folder 1)
    - *., April 19, 1942. (Box 26, Folder 1)
    - *., April 26, 1942. (Box 26, Folder 1)
    - *., May 3, 1942. (Box 26, Folder 1)
    - *., May 10, 1942. (Box 26, Folder 1)
    - *., May 17, 1942. (Box 26, Folder 1)
    - *., May 24, 1942. (Box 26, Folder 1)
    - *., May 31, 1942. (Box 26, Folder 1)
    - Special programs:. (Box 26, Folder 1)
      - *--Gulf Screen Guild Theatre, Parent by Proxy.., March 29, 1942. (Box 26, Folder 1)
      - *--Command Performance, U.S.A., Program #12.., May 3, 1942. (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - Other Programs.
    - *--Maxwell House Coffee Time.., November 21, 1940. (Box 16, Folder 4)
    - *--Bundles for Britain.., January 1, 1941. (Box 16, Folder 4)
    - *--Special Program for Radio and Movie Guide.., January 19, 1941. (Box 16, Folder 4)
    - *--America Calling.., February 8, 1941. (Box 16, Folder 4)
    - *--Behind the Mike, Benny Interview.., May 4, 1941. (Box 16, Folder 4)
    - *--Special broadcast from Benny's home, NBC 10th Anniversary Dinner.., May 9, 1941. (Box 16, Folder 4)
    - *--Millions for Defense.., July 30, 1941. (Box 16, Folder 4)
    - *--Tuesday Night Party.., May 16, 1939. (Box 22, Folder 3)
    - *--Screen Guild Show.., January 8, 1939. (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - The Grape Nuts Program.
    - ., October 4, 1942. (Box 26, Folder 2)
    - ., October 11, 1942. (Box 26, Folder 2)
    - ., October 18, 1942. (Box 26, Folder 2)
    - ., October 25, 1942. (Box 26, Folder 2)
    - ., November 1, 1942. (Box 26, Folder 2)
    - ., November 8, 1942. (Box 26, Folder 2)
    - ., November 15, 1942. (Box 26, Folder 2)
    - ., November 22, 1942. (Box 26, Folder 2)
    - ., November 29, 1942. (Box 26, Folder 3)
    - ., December 6, 1942. (Box 26, Folder 3)
    - ., December 13, 1942. (Box 26, Folder 3)
    - ., December 20, 1942. (Box 26, Folder 3)
    - ., December 27, 1942. (Box 26, Folder 3)
    - ., January 3, 1943. (Box 26, Folder 3)
    - ., January 10, 1943. (Box 26, Folder 3)
    - ., January 17, 1943. (Box 26, Folder 3)
    - ., January 24, 1943. (Box 26, Folder 3)
    - ., January 31, 1943. (Box 26, Folder 3)
    - ., February 7, 1943. (Box 27, Folder 1)
    - ., February 14, 1943. (Box 27, Folder 1)
    - ., February 21, 1943. (Box 27, Folder 1)
    - ., February 28, 1943. (Box 27, Folder 1)
    - ., March 6, 1943. (Box 27, Folder 1)
    - ., March 14, 1943. (Box 27, Folder 1)
    - ., March 21, 1943. (Box 27, Folder 1)
    - ., March 28, 1943. (Box 27, Folder 1)
    - ., April 4, 1943. (Box 27, Folder 2)
    - ., April 11, 1943. (Box 27, Folder 2)
    - ., April 18, 1943. (Box 27, Folder 2)
    - ., April 25, 1943. (Box 27, Folder 2)
    - ., May 2, 1943. (Box 27, Folder 2)
    - ., May 9, 1943. (Box 27, Folder 2)
    - ., May 16, 1943. (Box 27, Folder 2)
    - ., May 23, 1943. (Box 27, Folder 2)
    - ., May 30, 1943. (Box 27, Folder 2)
    - *., October 4, 1942. (Box 27, Folder 3)
    - *., October 11, 1942. (Box 27, Folder 3)
    - *., October 18, 1942. (Box 27, Folder 3)
    - *., October 25, 1942. (Box 27, Folder 3)
    - *., November 1, 1942. (Box 27, Folder 3)
    - *., November 8, 1942. (Box 27, Folder 3)
    - *., November 15, 1942. (Box 27, Folder 3)
    - *., November 22, 1942. (Box 27, Folder 3)
    - *., December 6, 1942. (Box 27, Folder 4)
    - *., December 13, 1942. (Box 27, Folder 4)
    - *., December 20, 1942. (Box 27, Folder 4)
    - *., December 27, 1942. (Box 27, Folder 4)
    - *., January 3, 1943. (Box 27, Folder 4)
    - *., January 10, 1943. (Box 27, Folder 4)
    - *., January 17, 1943. (Box 27, Folder 4)
    - *., January 24, 1943. (Box 27, Folder 4)
    - *., January 31, 1943. (Box 27, Folder 4)
    - *., February 7, 1943. (Box 28, Folder 1)
    - *., February 14, 1943. (Box 28, Folder 1)
    - *., February 21, 1943. (Box 28, Folder 1)
    - *., February 28, 1943. (Box 28, Folder 1)
    - *., March 14, 1943. (Box 28, Folder 1)
    - *., March 21, 1943. (Box 28, Folder 1)
    - *., March 28, 1943. (Box 28, Folder 1)
    - *., April 4, 1943. (Box 28, Folder 2)
    - *., April 11, 1943. (Box 28, Folder 2)
    - *., April 18, 1943. (Box 28, Folder 2)
    - *., April 25, 1943. (Box 28, Folder 2)
    - *., May 2, 1943. (Box 28, Folder 2)
    - *., May 9, 1943. (Box 28, Folder 2)
    - *., May 16, 1943. (Box 28, Folder 2)
    - *., May 23, 1943. (Box 28, Folder 2)
    - *., May 30, 1943. (Box 28, Folder 2)
    - ., October 10, 1943. (Box 28, Folder 3)
    - ., October 17, 1943. (Box 28, Folder 3)
    - ., October 24, 1943. (Box 28, Folder 3)
    - ., October 31, 1943. (Box 28, Folder 3)
    - ., November 7, 1943. (Box 28, Folder 3)
    - ., November 21, 1943. (Box 28, Folder 3)
    - ., November 28, 1943. (Box 28, Folder 3)
    - ., December 5, 1943. (Box 28, Folder 4)
    - ., December 12, 1943. (Box 28, Folder 4)
    - ., December 19, 1943. (Box 28, Folder 4)
    - ., December 27, 1943. (Box 28, Folder 4)
    - ., January 2, 1943. (Box 28, Folder 4)
    - ., January 9, 1943. (Box 28, Folder 4)
    - ., January 16, 1943. (Box 28, Folder 4)
    - ., January 23, 1943. (Box 28, Folder 4)
    - ., January 30, 1943. (Box 28, Folder 4)
    - ., February 6, 1944. (Box 28, Folder 4)
    - ., February 13, 1944. (Box 28, Folder 4)
    - ., February 20, 1944. (Box 29, Folder 1)
    - ., February 27, 1944. (Box 29, Folder 1)
    - ., March 5, 1944. (Box 29, Folder 1)
    - ., March 12, 1944. (Box 29, Folder 1)
    - ., March 19, 1944. (Box 29, Folder 1)
    - ., March 26, 1944. (Box 29, Folder 1)
    - ., April 2, 1944. (Box 29, Folder 1)
    - ., April 9, 1944. (Box 29, Folder 1)
    - ., April 16, 1944. (Box 29, Folder 2)
    - ., April 23, 1944. (Box 29, Folder 2)
    - ., April 30, 1944. (Box 29, Folder 2)
    - ., May 7, 1944. (Box 29, Folder 2)
    - ., May 14, 1944. (Box 29, Folder 2)
    - ., May 21, 1944. (Box 29, Folder 2)
    - ., May 28, 1944. (Box 29, Folder 2)
    - ., June 4, 1944. (Box 29, Folder 2)
- Television scripts.
  - The Jack Benny Program [Lucky Strike].
    - ., October 1, 1944. (Box 29, Folder 3)
    - ., October 8, 1944. (Box 29, Folder 3)
    - ., October 15, 1944. (Box 29, Folder 3)
    - ., October 22, 1944. (Box 29, Folder 3)
    - ., October 29, 1944. (Box 29, Folder 3)
    - ., November 5, 1944. (Box 29, Folder 3)
    - ., November 12, 1944. (Box 29, Folder 3)
    - ., November 19, 1944. (Box 29, Folder 3)
    - ., November 26, 1944. (Box 29, Folder 3)
    - ., December 3, 1944. (Box 29, Folder 4)
    - ., December 10, 1944. (Box 29, Folder 4)
    - ., December 17, 1944. (Box 29, Folder 4)
    - ., December 24, 1944. (Box 29, Folder 4)
    - ., December 31, 1944. (Box 29, Folder 4)
    - ., January 7, 1945. (Box 29, Folder 4)
    - ., January 14, 1945. (Box 29, Folder 4)
    - ., January 21, 1945. (Box 29, Folder 4)
    - ., January 28, 1945. (Box 30, Folder 1)
    - ., February 4, 1945. (Box 30, Folder 1)